Ivana Supljika

Nationality: Croatian Phone number: (+31) 642202842 Email address: ivana.supljika@gmail.com

in LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ivana-šupljika-7583b82b9/

Website: https://ivyshoo.github.io/

O Home: Zagreb (Croatia)

ABOUT ME

I'm a Creative Developer with a strong passion for Frontend Development and UI/ UX design. I have 2+ years of experience in designing and developing responsive landing pages for diverse clients. At a leading media company in SE Europe I was part of a productive interdisciplinary team that collaborated throughout 20+ projects.

Previous experiences in Sales and Digital Marketing as a Tech Support gave me a deep understanding of customer requirements and a strong inclination for swift, optimal solutions.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Frontend Developer / Designer

Hanza Media d.o.o. [01/02/2022 - 01/02/2024]

City: Zagreb | Country: Croatia | Website: https://www.linkedin.com/company/hanza-media/

- Design and development of landing pages (custom code) for Sales, Native advertising/ Sponsored content and Editorial staff projects + assistance in Wordpress and Joomla CMS
- UI/ UX Design: development, iteration and testing of design concepts and prototypes
- Custom tailored design solutions for product promotion to wide audiences
- · Work on various website templates for healthcare, financial, food & beverage, lifestyle and beauty industries
- Close team and department collaboration, constructive feedback sessions

AdOps Specialist

Hanza Media d.o.o. [01/01/2019 – 01/02/2022]

City: Zagreb | Country: Croatia | Website: https://www.linkedin.com/company/hanza-media/

- · Google Ad Manager: daily setup and monitoring of Display Ad campaigns + reporting on performance results
- Daily collaboration with Sales, Marketing and Design teams, substantial daily communication with clients
- Monthly financial reporting on Google Ad Network results
- Mentoring and training new team members

Sales assistant

Adidas Croatia d.o.o. [01/06/2016 – 31/12/2016]

City: Zagreb | Country: Croatia | Website: https://www.linkedin.com/company/adidas/

- Assistance to Key Account Manager during F/W 2016 and S/S 2017 season sales
- Setup of graphic presentations and apparel showroom in Adidas Croatia HQ

Advertising sales agent

Hrvatski Telekom d.o.o. [01/09/2015 – 31/12/2015]

City: Zagreb | Country: Croatia | Website: https://www.linkedin.com/company/hrvatski-telekom/

• Google Ads sales activities for leading telecommunications provider in Croatia (Deutsche Telekom subsidiary): digital advertising for clients from Small and Medium-sized Enterprises

EDUCATION AND TRAINING

Frontend development course

Algebra [01/11/2019 - 01/06/2020]

City: Zagreb | Country: Croatia | Website: https://www.linkedin.com/school/sveuciliste-algebra/

Digital design course

Algebra [01/03/2015 - 01/08/2015]

City: Zagreb | Country: Croatia | Website: https://www.linkedin.com/school/sveuciliste-algebra/

Master's degree in History

Faculty of Humanities and Social Sciences, University of Zagreb [01/09/2009 - 01/11/2013]

Website: https://web2020.ffzg.unizg.hr/

Bachelor's degree in History and Art History

Faculty of Humanities and Social Sciences, University of Zagreb [01/09/2005 - 01/09/2009]

Website: https://web2020.ffzg.unizg.hr/

SKILLS

Frontend development

HTML5 / CSS3 / SASS(SCSS) / Bootstrap / Responsive Design / JavaScript / GreenSock Animation Platform (GSAP) / Wordpress / Ele mentor / Version Control System (Git) / Github / Joomla / VS Code

Digital design

Adobe Illustrator / Adobe Photoshop / Adobe Animate / Adobe InDesign / UI/ UX design / Wireframes & Prototyping / Figma

General

Microsoft Office / Google Ad Manager / Project Management Tools (Notion, Trello)

ORGANISATIONAL AND INTERPERSONAL SKILLS

Skills

- Time Management accustomed to prioritizing main goals, meeting deadlines and being independent
- Communication clear and concise in written and verbal dialogue
- Teamwork eager to have productive collaboration with colleagues and to receive feedback
- Negotiation bridging the gap between company and client needs
- Mentoring onboarding new colleagues
- Learning and growth driven to expand skills and be in the loop with digital trends

LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): Croatian

Other language(s):

English German

LISTENING C2 READING C2 WRITING C1 LISTENING A2 READING A2 WRITING A2

SPOKEN PRODUCTION C1 SPOKEN INTERACTION C1 SPOKEN PRODUCTION A1 SPOKEN INTERACTION A1

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

PROJECTS

"Google Developer Challenge Scholarship", online course by Udacity, 2017/2018

"Managing the Arts: Marketing for Cultural Organizations", massive open online course by Leuphana Universitaet Lueneburg, 2015

HOBBIES AND INTERESTS

Gaming | Gardening | Architecture | Dogs